questionnaires = [
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 1,
        "question_text": "What are the basic instruments used for upcycling",
        "answer_correct": "Fabric-cutting scissors.",
        "answer2": "Paper-cutting scissors.",
        "answer3": "Clothes iron.",
        "answer4": "Sewing machine.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 2,
        "question_text": "Is it important to cut the fabric very straight?",
        "answer_correct": "No, it can be fixed in a later step.",
        "answer2": "No, it doesn't matter.",
        "answer3": "Yes, it is crucial.",
        "answer4": "We do not cut fabric when we upcycle.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 3,
        "question_text": "What can be used as a marker during upcycling",
        "answer_correct": "Bar soap.",
        "answer2": "Permanent marker.",
        "answer3": "Pen or pencil.",
        "answer4": "Needles.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 4,
        "question_text": "Can an item be upcycled without sewing?",
        "answer_correct": "Yes, a hidden safety pin can be used instead.",
        "answer2": "No, all upcycling methods require sewing.",
        "answer3": "Yes, upcycling doesn't need sewing.",
        "answer4": "No, there is no alternative to sewing when upcycling.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 5,
        "question_text": "On what kind of surface can you upcycle an item?",
        "answer_correct": "Flat surface.",
        "answer2": "Any surface.",
        "answer3": "You do not need a surface.",
        "answer4": "Rocky surface",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 6,
        "question_text": "Do upcycled items resemble the original item?",
        "answer_correct": "Not necessarily.",
        "answer2": "No, upcycling implies changing an item beyond recognition.",
        "answer3": "Yes, upcycling perserves the original purpose of the item.",
        "answer4": "Yes, upcycling does not dramatically alter the appearance of an item",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 7,
        "question_text": "Only one item can be upcyled at a time.",
        "answer_correct": "False, items can be combined during upcycling.",
        "answer2": "False, upcycling requires multiple items.",
        "answer3": "True, only one item can be repurposed.",
        "answer4": "True, upcycling always involves a minimum of three items for effectiveness.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 8,
        "question_text": "Only brand-new clothes can be upcycled.",
        "answer_correct": "False, any item of choice can be upcycled.",
        "answer2": "True, only brand new clothes can be upcycled.",
        "answer3": "False, only old clothes can be upcycled.",
        "answer4": "False, new items can be upcycled only if they have been worn at least once before.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 9,
        "question_text": "All fabrics can be cut in the same way while upcycling.",
        "answer_correct": "False, different fabrics require different cuts.",
        "answer2": "True, all fabric can be cut in the same way.",
        "answer3": "False, fabric is not cut during upcycling.",
        "answer4": "True, as long as they are made from synthetic materials.",
    },
    {
        "id_topic": 1,
        "id": 10,
        "question_text": "Can upcycling be done with only one type of clothing material, such as denim?",
        "answer_correct": "Yes, upcycling can focus on specific clothing materials like denim.",
        "answer2": "No, upcycling requires a mix of various clothing materials.",
        "answer3": "Yes, but only natural fabrics are suitable for upcycling.",
        "answer4": "No, upcycling is limited to brand-new clothing items.",
    }
]